blackwasp.co.uk 2012-12-27

# Privacy Policy :: BlackWasp Software Development

## Personal Information Collection

Your personal information will only be collected if you submit it to BlackWasp using the contact form. Your name, email address and any comments you make will be retained if you have specified that you permit this. If you elect not to have your details recorded by indicating that you do not want to be contacted then your details will be erased after your query is answered. If you later decide that you wish this information to be deleted, please request this using the contact form.

## Web Site Logs

Information is gathered automatically in the form of web site logs and using Google Analytics. This includes anonymous information such as your web service provider and IP address. The pages that you visit are recorded in these logs. This information is used for analysis purposes only to allow improvement to the site. No personal information is gathered in this manner.

## Use of Information

Your personal information may be used to contact you when new developments are made to the web site or when new articles or other items are published to the web site. Your information will not be distributed to third parties except where this becomes required by law. Your details will not be passed to third parties.

## Linked Web Sites

The BlackWasp web site contains links to other web sites. The privacy policy of these web sites may differ from that of the BlackWasp web site.

## Advertising

This web site is funded by advertising placements. The advertisement code may create cookies on your browser and reads the contents of these cookies. The advertisements may also use web beacons to collect browsing information. This information is not used, gathered or retained by BlackWasp. Some advertising on the BlackWasp web site is provided by the Google Adsense programme. This includes interest-based advertising. The following information relates to Google's system:

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the web site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this web site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

## Policy Changes

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. Changes to the policy will be made available via this web page.
